<u>CURRICULUM VITAE</u>

PERSONAL INFORMATION:

Name: Binh Nguyen Dinh

Sex: Male Age: 25

Nationality: Vietnamese Date of Birth: 15th May 1988. Place of Birth: Hai Duong Marial Status: Single

Address: 91/25A Street 20, Ward 6, GoVap District, Ho Chi Minh city

Telephone No: 0973018765 Email: ndbinh99@gmail.com

PROFILE:

I am a proficient developer with 3 years' Android app experience, Android developing and a track record of delivering quality solutions using a range of different technologies. Concentrating on Java, Android Framework and Objective - C for the past 2 years, I have extensive experience of using open source software and libraries to implement enterprise class applications in. I am seeking a challenging position as a software designer / senior developer, ideally in a project team developing large scale enterprise system.

QUALIFICATIONS / EDUCATION:

 2006-2010 Bachelor degree in Computer Science University of Natural Science, HCMC

CERTIFICATES / TRAINING:

• Gameloft Certificate of completion (gameloft internship program).

WORKING EXPERIENCES:

2010 January - 2012 July: works at TMA Solutions

2012 July - present: work as freelancer, at odesk and offsite

and

Mobile Development Team Leader	
TMA Calling Name TMA Solutions Aug 2011 Mobile app that help members among an organization access contact information of each other everywhere	Android 1.x,2.x,4.x Titanium
Duties:Implement Android and Titanium application	
Orderbolt Orderbolt Co. July 2012 – Sep 2012 App for smartphones that gives user the power to order and pay from your table by simply scanning a QR code Duties: • Develop Android, iPhone application	HTML5, Phonegap, Sencha Android 2.x,4.x iOS 5
TST Information Collector Toshiba Jun 2012 – Sep 2012 An application for engineer working in power plant. This app help engineer to collect data from turbine, generator and draw graph. Duties: Develop ipad application Fix bugs	iOS 5.x
Twig Twig-it Communications Denmark Feb 2012 – Jun 2012 A system that help business organization control, log, track calls or sms of employee.	Android 2.x,4.x Private API and Jailbroken iOS 4.x,5.x (MobileSubstrate, Theos, Logos)
 Duties: Implement Android application Implement iphone application 	
Wells Fargo Wells Fargo Dec 2011 – Feb 2012 Mobile and web app that help bank teller to deal with customer.	Black Berry 5,6,7 & HTML5
 Duties: Develop Black Berry application Develop HTML5 application Take part in giving solutions, develop and fix bug in difference functions. 	
Hooz It ZMS Jan 2011 – Jul 2011 Social network of people who use mobile devices	Android 1.x,2.x,4.x , Black Berry 5,6,7

This social network which help people to connect with others or create and manage their group across the US.

The system focuses on these functions:

- Connect people.
- Mange user information, parental control.
- · Group management and communication.
- Purchasing.

It also provides basic functionality for:

- Notification and reminder through message center.
- Google map.

Duties:

- Develop mobile application
- Bug fixing.

Bluetooth Android Server - Client

Toshiba Electric

The Android-client app that help users contact with server.

The android -client transfer command to server for getting data and showing that data on android tablet 'screen. And at android client, user can send command to turn off/on light, fan, screen related devices

Duties:

- o Project leader
- o design system architecture
- o development

SCTV Phone

The Android-client app that helps people connect and call each other.

Streaming is from SCTV line. The app is used as Viber

Duties:

o Project leader

TV360

Android app for being embedded on HDMI Stick.

Used to streaming Video from server to display on HDMI Television.

Duties:

- o Join development
- o Join design
- o Project management

Duration: 2 months

DiasporaTV

Android app for being embedded on Mini Android USB.
Used to streaming Video from server to display on HDMI Television.

Android 2.3++

Set Top Box Android & mini Android USB

Android 4.x

Duties: o Leader o Join design o Project management Duration: 2 months

KEY SKILLS:

Soft Skills:

- Team work (communicate, problem solving with my colleagues).
- Time management.
- Presentation
- Listening comprehension at work.
- Concentration skill & Responsibility.

Software Programming Skills:

- Android Development
- IOS development , Objective-C
- Strong OOP skills
- Data Base design.
- Java software Architecture, Design and Development (JSP & Servlets, EJB, JDBC, Web Services, Java Mail, Multithreading, Design patterns)
- Operating system: Windows, Mac OS, Google Android, Apple iOS, RIM Blackberry.
- IDE/Case Tools: Eclipse, xCode, jEdit
- MySQL/SQL/Oracle Development
- Open source libraries (Struts, Log4J, POI)
- Web / Application Servers (Apache, Tomcat)
- Database Servers (Oracle, MSSQL, MySQL)

Language Skills:

Written Proficiency Spoken Proficiency

Vietnamese Fluent Fluent English Fluent Fluent

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:

• Driving Licence: Full, clean licence.

References: Available on request.

HOBBIES / INTERESTS:

- Sport, Internet Marketing.
- Volleyball.
- Swimming.
- Hang out with family and friend.